<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RePass Cloud</title>
    <link>http://repasscloud.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on RePass Cloud</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://repasscloud.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introducing LunaVPN: Your Privacy-Powered Guardian</title>
      <link>http://repasscloud.com/posts/2023-12-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://repasscloud.com/posts/2023-12-19/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, online security and privacy have become paramount. As the demand for VPN (Virtual Private Network) services continues to rise, building a VPN service with modern technology has never been more relevant. In this guide, we will walk you through the steps to create your own VPN service using cutting-edge tools and technologies.&#xA;The Foundation: .NET Back-End At the heart of our VPN service lies Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embracing the Future: Repass Cloud&#39;s Latest Website Redesign</title>
      <link>http://repasscloud.com/posts/2023-12-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://repasscloud.com/posts/2023-12-11/</guid>
      <description>A Glimpse into Our Digital Evolution RePass Cloud is embarking on an exciting journey of transformation once again, and we couldn&amp;rsquo;t be more thrilled to share it with you. As we bid farewell to our previous website design, we welcome a fresh and modern look that encapsulates our unwavering commitment to innovation and adaptability.&#xA;The Move to Hugo: Embracing Modern Technology One of the most significant changes in our journey is the adoption of Hugo, a modern static site generator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Winget on Windows Server 2022</title>
      <link>http://repasscloud.com/posts/2023-10-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://repasscloud.com/posts/2023-10-27/</guid>
      <description>When setting up a lab environment for deploying Active Directory automation tools, we recognized the efficiency of using Winget to install software across multiple machines. However, Windows Server 2022 does not readily support Winget from Microsoft.&#xA;Our quest for solutions involved extensive research, with many references leading to more references. After navigating this information labyrinth, we decided to provide a quick guide for those looking to set up Winget on their Windows Server 2022 environment with minimal hassle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying Language and Regional Settings</title>
      <link>http://repasscloud.com/posts/2023-08-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://repasscloud.com/posts/2023-08-02/</guid>
      <description>Demystifying Language and Regional Settings: A Guide to Avoid Confusion As an SOE (Standard Operating Environment) Builder, configuring language and regional settings in Windows can be a perplexing challenge. Windows operating systems cater to diverse linguistic and cultural communities worldwide, making it essential to get these settings right. The AutoUnattend.xml file plays a pivotal role in automating the setup process, but the complexities of four critical settings - InputLocale, SystemLocale, UILanguage, and UserLocale - can often lead to confusion during customization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing our new design</title>
      <link>http://repasscloud.com/posts/2023-05-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://repasscloud.com/posts/2023-05-17/</guid>
      <description>Repass Cloud Evolves for a Dynamic Future RePass Cloud is thrilled to announce an exciting transition as we move away from our original website design and embrace a fresh, modern look that truly represents our commitment to innovation and adaptability. The launch of our new website marks a significant milestone in our journey, and we are excited to share this evolution with you.&#xA;Our decision to revamp the website stems from our dedication to providing the best user experience and keeping up with the ever-changing digital landscape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refund Policy</title>
      <link>http://repasscloud.com/legal/refund_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 02:24:08 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://repasscloud.com/legal/refund_policy/</guid>
      <description>RepassCloud Digital Subscription Products Refund Policy This policy applies to all digital products offered by RepassCloud, including but not limited to OptechX, WanderConnect, AirAtlasPro, ActivusX, and LunaVPN, which are available as monthly, 6-month, and annual subscriptions. Some products may have different tiers or levels of service.&#xA;1. Eligibility for Refunds Customers are eligible to request a prorated refund for the unused portion of their subscription at any time. If a customer contacts us within 2 days of the start of a new subscription period, they are eligible for a full refund of that period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming Soon: LunaVPN</title>
      <link>http://repasscloud.com/projects/lunavpn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://repasscloud.com/projects/lunavpn/</guid>
      <description>LunaVPN: Your Gateway to Online Privacy 🚀 Coming Soon! 🚀&#xA;Experience a new era of online privacy with LunaVPN. We&amp;rsquo;re bringing you a VPN service like no other.&#xA;Stay Tuned for: ✨ Cutting-Edge Technology: LunaVPN leverages WireGuard to provide lightning-fast and secure connections.&#xA;🔒 Isolated Instances: Each LunaVPN service is created specifically for you, ensuring your privacy and security.&#xA;🌐 Global Access: Access the internet securely from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OptechX</title>
      <link>http://repasscloud.com/projects/optechx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://repasscloud.com/projects/optechx/</guid>
      <description>About OptechX OptechX is a cutting-edge Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) product that revolutionizes the process of building custom Windows Operating System Environment (SOE)1 images. Our platform enables seamless deployment of these custom images from the cloud, on-premises infrastructure, or even via hardware.&#xA;With OptechX, you can effortlessly generate tailored and optimized Windows OS images without the complexities associated with managing package dependencies, application binary versions, SOE development rules, security protocols, best practices, and the latest patches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TigerGrab 「とらグラブ」</title>
      <link>http://repasscloud.com/projects/tigergrab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://repasscloud.com/projects/tigergrab/</guid>
      <description>Tiger Grab 「とらグラブ」 is your effortless solution for Windows users seeking to preserve their favorite online videos. With a user-friendly interface, this program simplifies the process of downloading videos from a variety of sharing platforms.&#xA;Never miss out on cherished memories that may vanish from the internet. Tiger Grab lets you effortlessly retrieve and store videos, ensuring they remain accessible for years to come.&#xA;Experience hassle-free downloads with the ability to resume interrupted transfers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WanderConnect</title>
      <link>http://repasscloud.com/projects/wanderconnect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://repasscloud.com/projects/wanderconnect/</guid>
      <description>WanderConnect WanderConnect is your versatile companion for exploring, connecting, and creating memorable experiences. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re planning a solo adventure, a romantic date, or a family outing, WanderConnect is here to inspire and guide you.&#xA;Discover enchanting locations for romantic dates, from cozy cafes to scenic parks and charming restaurants. WanderConnect provides recommendations, ratings, and reviews, helping you choose the perfect spot to impress your partner and create a special connection.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
